http://www.brainstorm-group.com/privacy-policy

Sign InJoin
HomeTrainingTraining Courses & ScheduleLearning PathsFace-to-FaceVirtualOn DemandLive OnlineGroup TrainingWays to saveAboutEventsAMS, NL (Mar 1-23)MI, FL (Mar 1-23)CH, IL (Apr 26-29)SF, CA (Jun 28 - Jul 1)HOU, TX (Jul 6 - Sep 10)LDN, UK (Sep 13 - Oct 7)DC (Sep 20-23)NYC, NY (Nov 15-18)CertificatesBusiness ArchitectureBusiness Process ManagementDigital BusinessAgile Business AnalysisOperational Excellence AssociateOperational Excellence ProfessionalDigital Decisioning & AnalyticsCertificationPrepareStudy MaterialsStudy GuideCoverage MapRegisterAboutSelf-AssessmentsResourcesArticlesWebcastsWhite PapersResearchBooksBPM JobsMembershipCommunity MemberPremium MemberProfessional MemberCorporate SponsorCompare MembershipsAccess Corporate Benefits
Facebook
Twitter
YouTube
LinkedIn
Home › Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy
BPMInstitute.org is committed to maximizing your experience and respecting your privacy.
This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information
(referred to as "Data" below) that may be collected by us on our site.
This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or
control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our
control. Please take time to read our Terms of Use.
Subscriptions
All our newsletter subscribers are
opt-in subscribers. All newsletter subscriptions have an opt-in date and
IP address proving that the opt-in event occurred. Every email that is
sent to our subscribers out comes with an unsubscribe link at the
bottom.
Data
Your user name, e-mail address, or other
submissions that you make on this site may contain your real name or
other personally identifiable information and, as a result, may appear
on this site. Like many web sites, we may also automatically receive
general information that is contained in our server log files such as
your IP address and cookie information.
Use of Data
We may use Data to customize and
improve your user experience on this site. We will make efforts so that
your Data will not be provided to third parties unless (i) provided for
otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) we obtain your consent, such as
when you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a
service provided on our site requires the interaction with or is
provided by a third party; (iv) pursuant to legal process or law
enforcement; (v) we find that your use of this site violates our this
Policy, Terms of Service, other usage guidelines or as deemed reasonably
necessary by us to protect our legal rights and/or property; or (vi)
this site is purchased by a third party whereby that third party will be
able to use the Data in the same manner as we can as set forth in this
Policy. In the event you choose to use links that appear on our site to
visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that
appear on those sites.
Cookies
Cookies (small pieces of information
that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive) enable us
to provide certain features such as retaining your login information so
you don't need to login with each visit. We also use cookies to provide
statistical information regarding site usage.
Sponsors and Advertisers
Our sites contain links
to Web sites outside the control of BPMInstitute.org. We encourage all
of our partners to implement policies and practices that respect the
privacy of users. However, BPMInstitute.org is not responsible for the
privacy practices or the content of linked web sites. BPMInstitute.org
shall have no liability whatsoever arising from any use by Sponsors that
is outside of our control.
Please note that we review our privacy practices from time to time,
and that such practices are subject to change. We ask that our visitors
review this page to ensure they understand the most current version of
our privacy statement. If you have any further questions please contact
us at info@BPMInstitute.org.
Editing or Deleting Your Account Information
BPMInstitute.org
uses email to communicate with members of the site. If at any time you
would like to unsubscribe from your email subscription, or you would
like to change the email address where you receive your subscription,
you can do so by following the links at the bottom of the email. You can
also email us. Please allow up to 48 business hours for any changes to
take effect. Content or other data that you may have provided to us and
that is not contained within your user account, such as posts that may
appear within our forums, may continue to remain on our site at our
discretion even though your user account is deleted. Please see our
Terms of Use for more information.
No guarantees
While this Privacy Policy states
our standards for maintenance of Data and we will make efforts to meet
them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may
be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a
consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to
maintenance or nondisclosure of Data.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Policy or our web site, please feel free to contact us at info@BPMInstitute.org.
Shopping cart
View your shopping cart.
Membership at BPMInstitute.org includes access to our other communities
BrainStorm Group © 2020 | Privacy Policy | ADVERTISE | ABOUT | CONTACT US                              US TOLL FREE: 1 (855) 300-2686
TOLL: 1 (508) 475-0475
x
Remind me later
New Members Save 15%
Join today to receive a 10-day Professional trial membership.You'll get unlimited access to content and save 15% on on demand and live online training courses during your trial.
